<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.10.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/docs/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/docs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-05-05T15:21:24-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/docs/feed.xml</id><title type="html">SD Updates</title><subtitle>Get your Service Desk news!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">The Year’s End</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/05/05/School-Year's-End.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Year’s End" /><published>2025-05-05T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2025-05-05T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/05/05/School-Year&apos;s-End</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/05/05/School-Year&apos;s-End.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="prologue">Prologue</h1>
<p>Howdy, friends 🤠
I’m so proud of your work these last two semesters. One of the joys of my job is to watch you grow and succeed. I know it seems trvial or anodyne work that anyone could do. But I don’t see it that way. You all achieve so much and are, in my eyes, building a solid foundation for your careers in the future.</p>

<h1 id="goodbye-i-guess">Goodbye, I guess.</h1>
<p>Seniors, congratulations and I wish you all the best. I have no doubt that all of you will succeed and thrive. SD grads have a practically 100% job placement rate out of school. Worst case, you have IT has a fallback. You are a valuable asset now. You are graduating with a degree <em>and</em> a technology toolbox. How many of your friends and peers have that same level of technicality. If you ever need recommendations, advice, or reassurance, reach out. Both Donavan and I are here to help you guys. If you want my phone number or anything to keep in touch, I’d be happy to give it to you. I’m also on Telegram and Matrix.</p>

<p>Returners, you guys <em>wish</em> you were the graduating seniors. Unless you’re Josh I guess. Have you seen those guys? ELITE. I’m not saying you guys <em>can’t</em> achieve what they did, but it’ll be work. I think you can get there though. You guys have a lot of potential in your tummies. Make sure you say your goodbyes to those that are leaving. Those include: Mara, David, Stella, Hadil, Ikrom, Brian, Hermela, Jake, etc. These are also amazing resources to contact once you begin your own graduation journey.</p>

<h1 id="work-stuff-now">Work stuff now!</h1>
<h2 id="smarthub-return-apocalypse">Smarthub return apocalypse</h2>
<p>I will be leaving on the 9th for a 10 day trip. This means that I will possibly miss you guys as you leave campus. That’s a bummer.</p>

<p>That being said, end of year means Smarthub returns! Oh man, oh boy, here it comes. I will be gone for that. I am relying on you guys to take ownership and total control of that process. It is of high importance we recover those devices.</p>

<p>The laptops are almost universally due May 14th by 5pm. This is the day after finals. I’m a little nervous, ngl (not gonna lie). Before I leave, I will be sending out an email to every student who has a loan reminding them. This will come from my own email address. As we enter the week of the 14th, set aside proper space to receive the computers. I usually tape off an area to delineate computers that are dropped off, computers that have been dropped off and returned, and computers that are dropped off, returned and wiped.</p>

<p>Please be very cognizant of what you are doing. Messing this up could literally cost students. Make sure to be diligent!</p>

<p>David, Jake, Ikrom, Hadil, Hermela, Joshua, and Garen. Take special note of the above. You all are working that day and will be handling all of this. Think of and devise some strategies in order to make that all come together.</p>

<h2 id="are-ya-winning-son">Are ya winning, son?</h2>
<p>The Superlatives are out! Look here: <a href="https://media.ithaca.edu/media/Spring+25+SD+Awards7secs/1_fz7cudkj">WOW!</a></p>

<p>I imagine you’ve also seen it on your TDX desktop, right? Uh huh.</p>

<p>I have your prizes if you got one. Watch the vid and stop by :)</p>

<h2 id="required-reading">Required Reading</h2>
<p><a href="https://claytonwramsey.com/blog/prompt/">I’d Rather Read the Prompt</a>
<a href="https://oxfordamerican.org/oa-now/the-alabama-landline-that-keeps-ringing">Just a silly story I felt you guys would identify with</a></p>

<p>I would love for you to read these and talk to me about how you feel. Get a “vibe check”, you know? Especially the first one.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prologue Howdy, friends 🤠 I’m so proud of your work these last two semesters. One of the joys of my job is to watch you grow and succeed. I know it seems trvial or anodyne work that anyone could do. But I don’t see it that way. You all achieve so much and are, in my eyes, building a solid foundation for your careers in the future.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">April reminders!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/04/09/End-of-Spring-Stuff.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="April reminders!" /><published>2025-04-09T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2025-04-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/04/09/End-of-Spring-Stuff</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/04/09/End-of-Spring-Stuff.html"><![CDATA[<p>Everyone! Isn’t this RSS feed nifty?</p>
<h1 id="first">First!</h1>

<h2 id="-yall-better-read-hadils-post">🚜 Y’all better read Hadil’s post</h2>
<p>She worked very hard on it and you owe her. <a href="https://teams.microsoft.com/l/message/19:621d99492590415c9db1f5c8f4284832@thread.skype/1744145558844?tenantId=fa1ac8f6-5e54-4857-9f0b-4aa422c09689&amp;groupId=32cbcebf-fc7b-4909-a75a-40b7122e30c9&amp;parentMessageId=1744145558844&amp;teamName=IT%20Service%20Desk&amp;channelName=Desk%20Announcements&amp;createdTime=1744145558844&amp;ngc=true">Annoucement!</a></p>

<h1 id="second">Second!</h1>

<h2 id="-its-coming-up-on-the-end-of-tax-season">🚗 It’s coming up on the end of tax season!</h2>
<p>and fresh alumni may still need to access Homer for tax info!
Here are some quick directions to guide students to their 1098-Ts:</p>
<ul>
  <li>Log into HomerConnect</li>
  <li>Click on “Billing and Payment” in the sidebar</li>
  <li>Click “Tax Notification (1098-T)”</li>
</ul>

<p>Also, take advantage of the Tax Clinics that Ben is offering in conjunction with Kari Smoker!</p>

<h1 id="third">Third!</h1>

<h2 id="-smarthub-is-slipping">🚒 Smarthub is slipping!</h2>
<p>Gamers, please please make sure that we are returning things in Smarthub. There have been many times now where I have seen us not return or not loan things properly. We have to be better. Please reach out to the person sitting next to you for help if you’re unsure.Remember that student chargers are only a 1 day loan!</p>

<h1 id="fourth-and-final">Fourth, and final</h1>

<h2 id="-please-refer-to-the-previous-desk-announcement">🚕 Please refer to the previous desk announcement</h2>
<p>about new student registration. Some of you definitely have not looked at that file I linked. Look at this image! See anything wrong? Why is it wrong?</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/notag.png" alt="tdx" /></p>

<p>I’m still finding hundreds, maybe thousands, of new student tickets without any tagging.</p>

<h3 id="why-not-read-this-short-blog-post">Why not read this short blog post?</h3>
<p>We can argue about it next shift if you want…
<a href="https://usher.dev/posts/2025-03-08-kill-your-feeds/">Here ya go</a>
<a href="https://www.audubon.org/news/surprisingly-long-history-movement-make-buildings-safer-birds">bonus article unlocked</a></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone! Isn’t this RSS feed nifty? First!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Break Achievements!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/14/Break-Achievements.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Break Achievements!" /><published>2025-03-14T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2025-03-14T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/14/Break-Achievements</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/14/Break-Achievements.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="welcome-back">Welcome back!</h1>

<p>I hope you all had a restful break. While most of you were sleeping till noon and ignoring your parent’s subtle pleas to cook <em>them</em> a dinner for once, some enterprising and ambitious students were hard at work at the Service Desk accomplishing more than I really thought we could!</p>

<h2 id="tdx-beautification">TDX Beautification</h2>

<p>What words come to mind when I say “Teamdynamix”? Boring? Drab? Mundane? Prosaic? Banal? Well, no more!
David, Garen, and Ikrom have poured their souls into making TDX a place that shows off IC’s natural beauty and embraces the bucolic surrounding of our little home away from home. Upon opening <a href="https://help.ithaca.edu">help.ithaca.edu</a> you will now be greeted by the sweeping green slopes of our practice fields and the lake beyond, the floral gardens so lovingly maintained, and the cerulean waters of the majestic fountains. It makes you want to sing 🎵”Ithaca, forever shine your light on me,
in my heart together we shall always be”🎵</p>

<p>Please thank them when you see them. They have truly left an indelible mark on IT with this. I’ll attach pictures below for your enjoyment.</p>

<h2 id="magical-forms-oh-my">Magical Forms, oh my!</h2>

<p>Josh, also, was fastened to the desk and furiously typing, brow firmly furrowed. He forged new forms most fondly. Fair, my fellow to figure for what this form facilitates. Forsooth, fathom no further. For he has faceted field after field to fabricate a form most fabled. Find this form, friend, festooned [here]. Frankly, I’m fully flabbergasted at his fortitude. He fights with a fiery furor that flumoxes me as he makes, in fact, fifteen fifty. Thanks F’Josh!</p>

<h2 id="pictures">Pictures!</h2>

<p><img src="/assets/images/tdxbuttonscolor.png" alt="buttons" />
<img src="/assets/images/tdxiconscolor.png" alt="icons" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Intercom Changes LIVE!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/12/Intercom-Change.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Intercom Changes LIVE!" /><published>2025-03-12T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2025-03-12T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/12/Intercom-Change</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/12/Intercom-Change.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="intercom-updates">Intercom updates</h2>
<p>Intercom is now be behind a login screen. Only current students, faculty, staff, and affiliates are able to view it. Retirees can as well, but not alumni. Review the Intercom article in the Teams General chat for more info. Be prepared for an influx of SSPR and DUO requests as people who have never had to sign in will now have to.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intercom updates Intercom is now be behind a login screen. Only current students, faculty, staff, and affiliates are able to view it. Retirees can as well, but not alumni. Review the Intercom article in the Teams General chat for more info. Be prepared for an influx of SSPR and DUO requests as people who have never had to sign in will now have to.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pre2013Alum Update to SSPR Form</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/06/Pre2013Alums.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pre2013Alum Update to SSPR Form" /><published>2025-03-06T11:20:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-03-06T11:20:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/06/Pre2013Alums</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/06/Pre2013Alums.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="pre-2013-alumni-requests">Pre-2013 Alumni Requests</h1>
<p>There has been an additional question added to the SSPR form. “Is this a request for an alumni that graduated before 2013?”. Answering yes to this questions gives another process for you to follow that is specific to Alumni who graduated before 2013. Check it out!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-2013 Alumni Requests There has been an additional question added to the SSPR form. “Is this a request for an alumni that graduated before 2013?”. Answering yes to this questions gives another process for you to follow that is specific to Alumni who graduated before 2013. Check it out!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Duo and SSPR response changes!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/06/SSPR-Duo-1-Day!.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Duo and SSPR response changes!" /><published>2025-03-06T09:02:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-03-06T09:02:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/06/SSPR-Duo-1-Day!</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/06/SSPR-Duo-1-Day!.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="1-day-response-window">1 day response window</h1>
<p>We are changing from a 3 business day to a 1 business day response time for SSPR and Duo tickets. This is all an effort to reduce the amount of tickets sitting in the queue. The logic is that if a user isn’t responding to getting access to their account, how urgent is it? Everything else stays the same when it comes to closing and how we respond.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[1 day response window We are changing from a 3 business day to a 1 business day response time for SSPR and Duo tickets. This is all an effort to reduce the amount of tickets sitting in the queue. The logic is that if a user isn’t responding to getting access to their account, how urgent is it? Everything else stays the same when it comes to closing and how we respond.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Toshiba Attribute</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/05/Toshiba-Attribute.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Toshiba Attribute" /><published>2025-03-05T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-03-05T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/05/Toshiba-Attribute</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/docs/2025/03/05/Toshiba-Attribute.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="printers-tdx-update">Printers TDX Update</h2>
<p>There is a new attribute in TDX to see if a printer is covered under Toshiba’s warranty! See if you can find it</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Printers TDX Update There is a new attribute in TDX to see if a printer is covered under Toshiba’s warranty! See if you can find it]]></summary></entry></feed>